Ravi (Ray) Yadav.

19A Fergusson Avenue, Sandringham, Auckland.

M: 0223418771 ravi.ry.yadav@gmail.com

Summary

Accomplished and energetic manager with a solid history of achievement in managing Business and organisation and participating in annual budget planning. Motivated leader with strong organizational prioritization abilities. Areas of expertise include maintain health and safety, recruiting, training, managing, controlling, budgeting and operating company service.

Skills

- Energetic and outgoing personal.
- Judgement and decision making.
- Complex problem solving.
- Operating monitoring.
- Public safety and security.

- Management and personal resources.
- Multitask and motivation.
- Quality control Analysis.
- Education and Training.

Experience

Company Manager

August 2019 to Present

CLEAN SCOPE NZ LTD

Duties

- Invoicing/ Payroll & paying to our contractor and suppliers.
- Making Quote for customers.
- Marketing and introducing new customers.
- Training staff and maintaining health and safety.
- Inspecting sites and taking feedback from customers.

Area Manager.

May ,2018 to July 2019.

Flawless cleaning service Ltd.

Hamilton Branch.

Duties

- Scheduling and assigning specific duties/roles to staffs and ensuring that they are carried out expertly.
- Recruit and train when required. Monitor staff performance and forward to Director any concerns relating to work performance and behaviour of staff.
- Hold and organise meetings with potential clients
- Monitoring and reviewing storage and inventory systems to meet supply requirements and control stock levels.
- Note any important feedback from customers regarding the before, during and after services provided and implement those suggestions when developing new policies or service standards.
- Participate in Annual Budget Planning with the owner using day to day sales, customer count and financial statistics of the current and previous years.
- Providing Quotes to the clients.
- Preparing roster.
- Paying staff, third party and invoicing customer.

Housekeeping supervisor

September 2014 - January 2017

Auckland Northshore motel and holiday park.

Duties:

- Train housekeepers on cleaning and maintenance tasks.
- Oversee staff daily.
- Check rooms and common areas, including stairways and lounge areas, for cleanliness
- Motivate team members and resolve any issues that occur on the job.
- Screens job applicants, hires new employees, and recommends promotions, transfers, and dismissals.
- Managing Time and Schedules.
- Managing Equipment and Supplies

Supervisor

10 February 2017 to May ,2018.

CleanZ professional cleaning company limited-Auckland central, 1010 Duties

- Operating company service teams on shift and maintaining all policies and standards of company.
- Direct activities of team member for effective contributions to the company operation, monitoring employee performance.
- Lead and manage all employees on shift, provide proper training according to company guidelines.
- Ensure team member follow correct maintenance procedures.

- Maintain health and safety of employees and our clients
- Order proper stock and also do inventory controlling.
- Conducts regular meetings with director
- Assist director to conduct marketing research, develop more networks of clients, and find new market opportunity
- Manage and control the cleaning site project on shift.
- Recommend or execute personnel actions, such as hiring, evaluations and promotions.
- Enforce safety and sanitation regulations.

Education

Diploma In business management level 6: Aug 2017.

Aspire2 International- Auckland.